( Watch on Kissasia.vip & KonFlix.vip )
You're sick.
Yes.
I'm sick.
Thanks for letting me know.
Otherwise, I'd still be in the dark.
Consider this money my consultation fee.
No, no, no.
Xiao Baojie said,
robbery
is an immoral act.
We doctors earn money
through our own skills.
I'm a doctor,
not a robber.
Let's go.
Wait for me here a moment.
Just now, when you were walking,
you put more weight on your right foot.
It must be an old injury
left from a fight back in the day.
Can you cure it?
No.
But it can help prevent the next flare-up.
Safflower oil.
Works great.
How much?
Just what you pulled out of your pocket.
So,
how is this any different from robbery?
Of course there is.
A whole lot easier.
Miracle doctor!
Thank you.
Xiao Baojie was right.
Earning money through your own skills,
that's the right way.
I'd rather go to hell
than go to Black Street.
Truly Black Street's golden words.
Charging me 3,000 was bad enough,
but it's actually expired!
Black Street.
Haven't they been laying low for a while?
The Madman of Central Street.
Doctor Su Yang.
In all the files about Black Street,
a child named Tongtong is often mentioned.
Black Street's beloved.
It's time to pay Black Street a visit.
To Black Street.
Later,
keep your distance from me.
I want to walk by myself.
So this is Black Street?
Looks pretty ordinary.
You're sick.
Are you talking to me?
I said, you're sick.
Buddy, how can you tell?
I can cure it.
How?
Since you're in Black Street,
you must know the Black Street Madman.
He's the only doctor in Black Street
with a valid medical license.
This bottle of medicine is from him.
This is just safflower oil.
But this is the Madman's medicine!
Are you sure you don't want it?
How much?
Fifty thousand.
A fair price for all.
Fifty thousand?
On Black Street,
rich boys like you die the fastest.
Maybe at a critical moment,
this bottle could save your life.
This represents the Madman's friendship.
And
what if I refuse?
You shouldn't refuse.
For someone like you,
fifty thousand
is just the cost of a dinner.
I only make 3,000 a month.
What you see here
is all I own.
I even bought this watch on installments.
Then trade me your watch for it.
No way.
Absolutely not.
What are you laughing at?
Can't you see he's about to kill me?
Get over here!
The salary I pay you
includes security duties.
Hurry up!
Come on.
You think I want to kill you?
Could she even stop me?
I have to say,
even I have no idea
where my dad found this girl.
Must've forgotten to check the almanac.
What kind of freaks am I running into?
But once the Immortal Realm descends,
what makes this world interesting is,
until the very last moment,
nobody knows
how it's all going to end.
Devouring heaven and earth,
holding the cosmos within.
Taotie!
Uh, I'll leave this to you, okay?
The Way of Heavenly Fire,
raging flames surging.
Zhurong!
Are you here for treatment,
or are you here to see me?
I...
What are you doing?
He's going to kill you.
I can can't stop him.
Are you guys here to fight?
Perfect, I'm quite bored.
I'm the Madman of Central Street.
We're here to talk,
not to fight.
He has no reason
to just kill me for no reason, okay?
Not here to fight.
A few days ago,
a gate rose up right in this spot.
Do you remember it?
Yeah, I remember.
I opened it.
So you're the Gate Opener.
In that case,
the changes happening in this world now,
you must already know about.
So I won't need to elaborate.
What I want to say is,
though Shanhai City seems normal now,
this situation won't last long.
Because human growth
is often accompanied by desire.
The Blessed Ones of Shanhai City,
as time goes on,
won't be content with the status quo.
They'll develop their own ambitions.
And it's not just Shanhai City.
Other cities will face the same thing,
including the Imperial Capital,
which is also full of factions,
ready to make a move.
I plan to establish a brand new division,
a division composed of Blessed Ones,
and its name will be
Lingxiao.
I now represent Shanhai City
to formally invite you to join us,
and serve as the captain.
You're blocking my sunlight.
Impossible.
From where I'm sitting,
I mean,
there's no way from this spot I could...
You're blocking my sunlight.
Sunlight.
Time is of the essence.
I don't want to waste it.
Would you like to hear
the terms I'm offering?
If you're really short on people,
there's a Simpleton over on East Street.
Pretty easy to fool.
Are you sure you won't reconsider?
Your so-called Black Street,
actually isn't as safe
as you think it is.
Are you threatening me?
If possible,
I'd prefer a gentler approach
to begin our cooperation.
A bunch of nosy busybodies.
Was this
done by your people?
No.
They're just
some bored neighbors, that's all.
By the way,
most of them have mental issues too.
Did I just now
come across as
a little too overconfident?
Exactly.
That "who else but me" feeling,
was unmistakable.
Do I still have a chance to leave alive?
Of course.
I promised Xiao Baojie
I wouldn't kill people randomly.
I'm looking forward to our next meeting.
You're strong.
I want to fight you.
Do you have insurance?
I do.
Disability and accident insurance, both.
Bring it on.
You've got some strength,
but you've got to actually hit me.
The weather's really nice today.
What are we having for dinner?
Anything works.
How about
we have barbecue?
The kind we grill ourselves.
I'm actually pretty good at grilling meat.
Sure, let's have barbecue!
Okay.
That's a great idea.
You damn Limpy.
Is there no room for you on West Street?
Why do you keep coming to Central Street?
Tongtong gave it to me.
Oh, you damn Limpy!
Coming here to show off.
Tongtong!
I'm here, Tongtong.
They said you made something delicious.
Big Brother Simpleton.
Here.
This green tea is really good.
Sooner or later I'll kill this Simpleton.
Not bad.
He's too good at this.
Forget it, let's skewer the meat.
Big Brother Su Yang,
Uncle Limpy,
aren't you going to join us?
It's really fun.
Come on over, Big Brother Su Yang.
You!
Big Brother Simpleton!
Simpleton, stealing my chicken again?
Beat him up!
Let's eat together.
Tongtong, you eat too.
Here.
Smells pretty good.
Don't rush, I'll grill more.
Great, grill plenty.
Not bad.
Is there any more?
So delicious.
Yes, there is.
Here, here, take it.
There's more, there's more.
Good.
Isn't it still raw?
It's done, it's done.
The taste is really great.
I'm taking this skewer.
Here you go.
That skewer is mine.
I've eaten too much.